## **BO LAN**

356 Princeton St., East Boston, MA, 02128; 857-350-7615 lan.b@husky.neu.edu; http://wealthlibre.info/blog

### **SUMMARY:**

Long term experiences in web server management, coding open source programs, and 3D designed would build an innovative and productive work environment. The diversity management and multi-language skills should be great for every communication position. Great accounting experience and financial skills would provide a benefit to corporations to manage costs, investments, and other financial transactions.

### **EDUCATION:**

Master of Science in Leadership: Financial Market and Institution

May 2014

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

Certified General Accountant Students Program

September 2008 - Present

Beijing Branch of Certified General Accountants Association of Canada, Beijing, China

Bachelor of Management in Financial Management

May 2011

Accounting School, Huanghe Science and Technology College, Zhengzhou, Henan, China

#### SKILLS:

Computer Design Skills: Libreoffice, LaTeX, Gimp, Inkscape, Kdenlive Video Editor, Audacity Audio Editor, Blender 3D, Emacs Text Editor, Scribus

**Information Technologies:** C/C++, Python, CSS, HTML, Javascript, SQL Database, GTK+, Google App Engine, Blener Game Engine, OGRE 3D Engine.

Operating Systems: GNU/Linux, Mac Os X

Accounting & Finance: GAAP, Financial Statements, Journal Entries, Contribution Margin & Cost Management, Auditing & Working Paper, Consolidated financial statements, Investment Analysis

Accounting & Auditing Softwares: SAGE Accpac, Caseware: Working Paper, GnuCash, Yongyou U8 Solution

Languages: English, Mandarin, Cantonese

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES:

Nanning Bicycle Network Company- http://www.nnzxc.com

Co-founder, Organizer, Web manager

Nanning, Guangxi, China
October 2003 - September 2011

- Managed, operated, and promoted a commercial website which sells bikes. This website is used PHP, MySql technologies, and the Dicuz! bbs framework.
- Taught athletes and other employees how to communicate, race, do business, promote the company under the information and international circumstance. Organized and hosted races and training events for professional athletes.

#### Nanning Xiantong Electronic Commerce LLC.

Nanning, Guangxi, China

Assistant Accountant, Cost Manager Assistant

June 2010 – September 2010

- Recorded journal entries and assisted the accountant and other managers. Analyzed financial statements, and assisted managers for cost management decisions.
- Classified and managed electronic inventories, and match cost accumulation to inventories.

### OTHER ACTIVITIES:

Wealth & Libre – http://wealthlibre.info/

Boston, MA

Indie Web Developer, Finance Analyst, Arts Designer

December 2013 - Present

- Develop this web base on Python, CSS, Html5, and Javascript. Design art contents for this web by Gimp, Inkscape.
- Write and release finance, leadership, and free software information through this web page.

# Northeastern University Cycling Team

Boston, MA

Athlete, Organizer, Volunteer

september 2011 – Present

- $\bullet$  Organize, host riding and race at Eastern Collegiate Cycling Conference.
- Race bike at Eastern Collegiate Cycling Conference.